Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- State (PA) Wide Reports, 1936-1982; IV.
  - "Possibilities for Reduction in the Number of Units of Local Government", December, 1947
  - "The Potential for Effective Labor-Management relation in the Pittsburgh Region", November, 1957
  - "A Proposal Concerning State Authority Financing of Local School Construction", January, 1956
  - "Public Assistance Administration: A Three Year Review", February, 1975
  - "Relative Tax Cost to Manufacturing Industry", November, 1956
  - "Report and Recommendations on Storeskeeping and Procurement Functions – Department of Revenue", June, 1949
  - "Report of Audit of Implementation of Recommendations of the Governor's Review as of June 30, 1976", 1975
  - "Report of Audit of Implementation of Recommendations of the Governor's Review as of December 31, 1976", 1975
  - "Report of Audit of Implementation of Recommendations of the Governor's Review as of December 31, 1977", 1975
  - "Report of Audit of Implementation of Recommendations of the Governor's Review as of September 30, 1977", 1975
  - "Report of Task Force on Non-Business Taxes – Governor's Tax Study and Revision Commission", June 30, 1978
  - "Report of The Hospital Cost and Utilization Committee", October 28, 1965 (Box 38)
  - "Report on a Study of the Comptroller System of the Commonwealth of PA", January 9, 1958
  - "Report to Governor Arthur H. James on PA's Bill for Government Covering the Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1940 – Supplement ", November, 1940
  - "Report to Governor Arthur H. James on PA's Bill for Government during the Fiscal Years Ending June 30, 1938 and June 30, 1939, including PA's Contribution to the Maintenance of the Federal Government and the Benefits Derived from the Federal Government"
  - "Report to Joint State Government Commission on Finances of the Commonwealth", February, 1939
  - "Report to Local Government Commission on Election Costs", Date not given
  - "Report to the Edward Martin (Governor) on the Budget of the Commonwealth of PA for the 1943-45 Biennium", April 10, 1943
  - "Report to the Governor and the Joint Appropriations Committee of the Senate and the House of Representatives – on the General Fund Budget of the Commonwealth of PA for the 1945-1948 Biennium", March 21, 1945
  - "Report to the Joint State Government Commission of the Commonwealth of PA on Relief in PA and Other States", April, 1940
  - "Report to the Joint State Government Commission of the Commonwealth of PA on the State Tax System of PA and Comparison with the Systems of Neighboring Industrial Systems", March, 1940
  - "Research Materials on State Finance", January 19, 1959
  - "Research Materials on State Finance - Supplement", January 26, 1959
  - "Research Materials on State Finance - Supplement II", February 2, 1959
  - "Revenue Policies for Cities of the Third Class", December, 1936
  - "Sewage: A New Concept of Treatment for the Small Community – At less cost", January, 1965
  - "State Level Voluntary Planning in the Health and Welfare Fields", January, 1965
  - "State-Local taxation of Public Utilities in PA", January, 1982
  - "Study of Hospital Utilization", November 30, 1966
  - "A Suggested Plan for the Organization of the Governor's Office of the Commonwealth of PA", December 9, 1954
  - "Summary of PA State Association of County Commissioners on Tax Assessment in PA Counties of the Fourth to Eighth Classes", September, 1940
  - "Summary & Supplementary Report to the Governor and the Joint Appropriations Committee on the General Fund Budget of the Commonwealth of PA for the 1945-1947 Biennium", March 21, 1945
  - "Survey – Bureau of Purchases – Department of Property and Supplies", September 10, 1947
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry: A Comparative Study of State-Local Tax Costs", December, 1962
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry", December, 1967
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry (1967) Supplement", March, 1969
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry (1967) - Supplement II", June 12, 1970
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry (1967) - Supplement II - Revised", July 7, 1970
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry: A Comparative Study of State-Local Tax Costs", March, 1972
  - "Taxes Paid by Industry: A Comparative Study of State-Local Tax Costs", October, 1974
  - "The Joint State Government Commission of the Commonwealth of PA on Relief in Three Southern States Compared to PA", 1940
  - "Urban Mass Transit in Pennsylvania", December, 1966